Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1 MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities: 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 60)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities: 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 480-481)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities: 1976 & Later (Offsite-box 481, Folder 2-3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Out @ Time-Inc (Offsite-box 481, Folder 4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 6)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 7)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1976 & Later (Offsite-box 481, Folder 8)
  - Personnel & Organization: Strike: Jan.-May 1976 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 9-11)
  - Personnel & Organization: Strike: June-Dec. 1976 (Offsite-box 481)
  - Personnel & Organization: Strike: June-Dec. 1976 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 14)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1970: Jan.-May (Offsite-box 481, Folder 15)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1970: June (Offsite-box 481, Folder 16)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1970: July-Aug. (Offsite-box 481, Folder 17)
  - Personnel & Organization: 1970: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 481, Folder 18)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1971 (Offsite-box 481)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1971 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1972 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 20)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1973 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 21)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1974 & Later (Offsite-box 481, Folder 22)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1961 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 23)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1962 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 24)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1963 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 25)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1964 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 26)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1965 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 1)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1966 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 2)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1967 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1968 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1969 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1970 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 6)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1971 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 7)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1972 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 8)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1973 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 9)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1974 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 10)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1975 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 11)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1976 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 12)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1977 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 13)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1978 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 14)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1979 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 15)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1980 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 16)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1981 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 17)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1982 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 18)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1983 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 19)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1984 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 20)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1985 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 21)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1986 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 22)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1987 (Offsite-box 482)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1987 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1988 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 24)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1989 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 25)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1990 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 26)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1991 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 1)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1992 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 2)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1993 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1994 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1995- (Offsite-box 483, Folder 5)
  - Pioneer Press: 1968-1969: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 483)
  - Pioneer Press: 1968-1969: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Pioneer Press: 1969: Hollister Publishing (Offsite-box 483)
  - Pioneer Press: 1969: Hollister Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Pioneer Press: 1970: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 483)
  - Pioneer Press: 1970: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Pioneer Press: 1971 & Later: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 483, Folder 10)
  - Pioneer Press: 1970-1971: Pickwick Papers (Offsite-box 483)
  - Pioneer Press: 1970-1971: Pickwick Papers [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Popular Science: Edit (Offsite-box 483, Folder 12)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1961: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 483, Folder 13)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1962: Pre-Publication (1) (Offsite-box 483, Folder 14)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1962: Pre-Publication (2) (Offsite-box 483)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1962: Pre-Publication (2) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1963 (Offsite-box 483)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1963 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1964 (Offsite-box 483)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1964 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1970 (Offsite-box 483)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1970 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Printing Developments, Inc. (PDI) (Offsite-box 483, Folder 20)
  - Production: 1992 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 21)
    Formerly Magazine Manufacturing & Distribution.
  - Promotion: Corporate [empty] (Offsite-box 483, Folder 22)
  - Public Affairs: Corporate: 1961-: General (Offsite-box 483, Folder 23-24)
  - Public Affairs: Corporate: 1961: Publicity: Der Speigal (Offsite-box 483, Folder 25)
  - Public Affairs: Corporate: 1963: Publicity: Fact (Offsite-box 483)
  - Public Affairs: Corporate: 1963: Publicity: Fact [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Public Affairs: Corporate: 1961-: Publicity: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 483, Folder 27)
  - Real Estate: Corporate (Offsite-box 483)
  - Real Estate: Corporate [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Real Estate: Corporate: 1961: Denver Shopping Center (Offsite-box 483, Folder 29)
  - Real Simple: 1999-: Edit and Pub. (Offsite-box 483, Folder 30)
  - St. Francisville Paper Co. (Offsite-box 483, Folder 31)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission Filings: 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 877)
    Scope and Contents
    The Securities and Exchange Commission filings include correspondence and forms regarding changes in the board of directors and other major events, details of mergers, purchase or sale of Time Inc. stock, and registration of securities. Forms filed primarily include Form 4, Form S-8, Form 8-K and Form 10-K. Time Inc. staff handling the filings include John F. Harvey (Comptroller), Curtis Messinger (Assistant Comptroller), and P. Peter Sheppe (Director of Administrative Services, part of the Comptroller's office).
  - Securities and Exchange Commission Filings: 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 878)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission Filings: 1974 (Offsite-box 879)
  - Selling Areas Marketing, Inc. (Offsite-box 483-484)
  - Southern Progress Corp. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 3)
  - Silver Burdett [empty] (Offsite-box 484, Folder 4)
  - Spectradyne, Inc. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 5)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1961: Edit: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 484, Folder 6)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1961: Edit: July-Aug. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 7)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1961: Edit: Oct.-Dec. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 8)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1961: Publishing: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 484, Folder 9)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1961: Publishing: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 10)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1962: Edit: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 484, Folder 11)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1962: Edit: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 12)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1962: Publishing: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 484, Folder 13)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1962: Publishing: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 14)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1963: Edit: Jan.-Aug. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 15)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1963: Edit: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 16)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1963: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 17)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1964: Edit (Offsite-box 484)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1964: Edit [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1964: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 19)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1965: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 20)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1965: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 21)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1966: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 22)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1966: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 23)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1967: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 24)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1967: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 25)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1968: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 26)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1968: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 27)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1969: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 28)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1970: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 30)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1970: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 31)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1971: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 32)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1971: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 33)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1972: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 34)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1972: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 35)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1973: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 36)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1973: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 37)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1974: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 38)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1974: Publishing [empty] (Offsite-box 484, Folder 39)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1974: International Activities: Jan.-May (Offsite-box 484, Folder 40)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1974: International Activities: June-Dec. (Offsite-box 484, Folder 41)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1975: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 42)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1975: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 43)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1976: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 44)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1976: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 45)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1977: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 46)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1977: Publications (Offsite-box 484, Folder 47)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1978: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 48)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1978: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 49)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1979: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 50)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1979: Publication (Offsite-box 484, Folder 51)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1980: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 52)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1980: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 53)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1981: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 1)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1981: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 2)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1982: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 3)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1982: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1983: Edit (Offsite-box 484, Folder 5)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1983: Publishing (Offsite-box 484, Folder 6)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1984: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 485, Folder 7)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1985: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 9)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1985: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 10)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 485, Folder 11)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1986: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 12)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1987: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 13)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1987: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 14)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1988: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 15)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1988: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 16)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1989: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 17)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1989: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 18)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1990: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 19)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1990: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 20)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1991: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 21)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1991: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 22)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1992: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 23)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1992: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 24)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1993: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 25)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1993: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 26)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1994: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 27)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1994: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 28)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1994: 40th Anniversary (Offsite-box 485, Folder 29)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1995: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 30)
  - Sports Illustrated: 2003-2004: 50th Anniversary Issues and Related Events (Offsite-box 485, Folder 31)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1995: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 32)
  - Sports Illustrated for Kids: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 33)
  - Sports Illustrated for Kids: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 34)
  - Sports Illustrated for Women: 1999-: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 35)
  - Sports Illustrated for Women: 1999-: Publication [empty] (Offsite-box 485, Folder 36)
  - Sports Illustrated International: 1990- (Offsite-box 485, Folder 37)
  - Sports Illustrated Japan: 1986 (Offsite-box 485, Folder 38)
  - Sports Illustrated on Campus (Offsite-box 485, Folder 39)
  - Student Life (Offsite-box 485, Folder 40)
  - Suede (Offsite-box 485, Folder 41)
  - Sunset Publishing Corporation (Offsite-box 485, Folder 42)
  - Syndication: 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 485, Folder 43)
  - Syndication: 1966-1973 (Offsite-box 485)
  - Syndication: 1966-1973 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - TDS Ventures, Inc.: Magazine Distribution (Joint Venture with New York Times) (Offsite-box 485, Folder 46)
  - TDS - Hatchette Litigation: 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 485)
  - TDS - Hatchette Litigation: 1990-1993 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - TDS - Hatchette Litigation: 1992 (Offsite-box 485, Folder 48)
  - Teen People: 1998-: Edit (Offsite-box 485, Folder 49)
  - Teen People: 1998-: Publishing (Offsite-box 485, Folder 50)
  - Teen People Online (Offsite-box 485, Folder 51)
  - Teletext (Offsite-box 485, Folder 52)
  - Temple Eastex, Inc.: 1961-1983 (Offsite-box 485-486)
  - Temple-Inland Inc.: 1983- (Offsite-box 486, Folder 2)
  - This Old House (Offsite-box 486, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1961: Edit: "Any Time, Every Time" (Offsite-box 2220, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1961: Edit: Comment: Bill Furth's Report (Offsite-box 486, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1961: Edit: Comment: Misc (Offsite-box 486, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1961: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 486, Folder 6-7)
  - Time: 1961: Publishing (Offsite-box 486, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1962: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 486, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1962: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 486, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1962: Publishing (Offsite-box 486, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1963: Anniversary, 40th (Offsite-box 486, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1963 and Before: Edit: Law Dept (Offsite-box 486, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1963: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 486, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1963: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 486, Folder 15)
  - Time: 1963: Publishing (Offsite-box 486, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1964: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 486, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1964: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 486, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1964: Publishing (Offsite-box 486, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1965: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 486, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1965: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 486, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1965: Publishing (Offsite-box 486, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1966: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 486)
  - Time: 1966: Edit: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time: 1966: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 486, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1966: Publishing (Offsite-box 486, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1967: Edit: Senior Editors Meeting: 9/17-9/18 (Offsite-box 486-487)
  - Time: 1967: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 487, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1967: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 487, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1967: Publishing (Offsite-box 487, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1968: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 487, Folder 5)
  - Time: Edit: Time Writers' Bermuda Conference: 10/6-7/68 (Offsite-box 487, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1968: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 487, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1968: Publishing (Offsite-box 487, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1968-1971: Publishing" "Power of Print" (Offsite-box 487, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1969: Senior Editors Conference: Nassau (Offsite-box 487, Folder 10-11)
  - Time: 1969: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 487, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1969: Edit: Misc: Jan-March (Offsite-box 487)
  - Time: 1969: Edit: Misc: Jan-March [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time: 1969: Edit: Misc: April-June (Offsite-box 487, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1969: Edit: Misc: July-Sept (Offsite-box 487, Folder 15)
  - Time: 2/2/1969: Edit: Senior Editors Conference (Offsite-box 487, Folder 16-18)
    Includes audiovisual material.
    1 audiotape reel: analog, 1 7/8 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Case Labeled: "(3) Sunday Evening Meeting, 10:30 PM - Midnight, Time Senior Editors Conference, GOOD"
    1 audiotape reel: analog, 1 7/8 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Case Labeled: "(2) Sunday Afternoon Meeting (2 1/2 hours) plus H. Donovon's after dinner talk 9 (only copy), Reward". Reel labeled "#4".
    1 audiotape reel: analog,1 7/8 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Case Labeled: "(1) Senior Editors Conference, Feb 2 1969, Sunday Morning Session, 10AM - 1PM, (3 hours), GOOD?"
  - Time: 1969: Edit: Misc: Oct-Dec (Offsite-box 487, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1969: Publishing (Offsite-box 487, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1970: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 487, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1970: Edit: Misc: Jan-Mar (Offsite-box 487, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1970: Edit: Misc: April-June (Offsite-box 487, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1970: Edit: Misc: July-Sept (Offsite-box 487, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1970: Edit: Oct-Dec (Offsite-box 487, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1970: Publishing (Offsite-box 487)
  - Time: 1970: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time: 1971: Edit: Misc: Jan-March (Offsite-box 487, Folder 27)
  - Time: 1971: Edit: Misc: April-June (Offsite-box 488, Folder 1)
  - Time: 1971: Edit: Misc: July-Sept (Offsite-box 488, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1971: Edit: Misc: Oct-Dec (Offsite-box 488, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1971: Edit: "Young or New Writers" Meeting: 11/23/71 (Offsite-box 488, Folder 4)
    1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Taped at 3 3/4 speed by E. Taylor, 11/23/71, Started at zero hundred, for H. Grunwald - "Young or New Writers" Group, Speaker: 1st H. Grunwald, 2nd E. Jamieson". Additional notes about the conference and speakers are also included on the case.
  - Time: 1971: Publishing (Offsite-box 488, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1972: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 488, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1972: Edit: Misc: Jan-March (Offsite-box 488, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1972: Edit: Misc: April-June (Offsite-box 488, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1972: Edit: Misc: July-Sept (Offsite-box 488, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1972: Edit: Misc: Oct-Dec (Offsite-box 488, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1972: Publishing: Production Consolidation Staff Study (Offsite-box 488, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1972: Publishing (Offsite-box 488, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1973: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 488)
  - Time: 1973: Edit: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time: 1973: Publishing (Offsite-box 488, Folder 15)
  - Time: 1974: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 488, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1974: Publishing (Offsite-box 488, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1975: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 488, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1975: Edit: Bicentennial Issue: Special 1776 Issue (Offsite-box 488, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1974-1975: Edit: Bicentennial Issue: Special 1776 Issue (2) (Offsite-box 488)
  - Time: 1974-1975: Edit: Bicentennial Issue: Special 1776 Issue (2) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time: 1975: Seminar (Edit/Publish) (Offsite-box 488, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1975: Publishing: Simmons (Offsite-box 488, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1975: Publishing (Offsite-box 488, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1976: Edit: Bicentennial Issue (Offsite-box 488, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1976: Edit: Bicentennial: Message to Amer (Offsite-box 488, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1976: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 489, Folder 1)
  - Time: 1976: Publishing: Simmons (Offsite-box 489, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1976: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1977 and Later: Edit: Synanon (Offsite-box 489)
  - Time: 1977 and Later: Edit: Synanon [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time: 1977: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 489, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1977: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1978: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 489, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1978: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1979: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 489, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1979: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1979: Publishing: Gulf + Western: Ad section 2/5/79 (Offsite-box 489, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1980: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 489, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1980: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 489, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1981: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 15)
  - Time: 1982: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 489, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1982: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1983: 60th Anniversary Issue (Offsite-box 489, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1983: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 489, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1983: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1984: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 489, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1984: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1985: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1985: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1986: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1986: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1987: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 27)
  - Time: 1987: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1988: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1988: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 30)
  - Time: 1989: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 31)
  - Time: 1989: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 32)
  - Time: 1990: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 33)
  - Time: 1990: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 34)
  - Time: 1991: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 35)
  - Time: 1991: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 36)
  - Time: 1992: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 37)
  - Time: 1992: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 38)
  - Time: 1993: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 39)
  - Time: 1993: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 40)
  - Time: 1993: 70th Anniversary (Offsite-box 489, Folder 41)
  - Time: 1994: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 42)
  - Time: 1994: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 43)
  - Time: 1995: Edit (Offsite-box 489, Folder 44)
  - Time: 1995: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 45)
  - Time: 1996: Publishing (Offsite-box 489, Folder 46)
  - Time: 1998: 75th Anniversary (Offsite-box 489, Folder 48)
  - Time: 2000: Edit: Presidential Election: Gore, Al (Offsite-box 490, Folder 1)
  - Time: 2003: Edit (Offsite-box 490, Folder 2)
  - Time: 2003: 80 Days (Offsite-box 490, Folder 3)
  - Time Asia: 2000-: Edit (Offsite-box 490, Folder 4)
  - Time Australia (Offsite-box 490, Folder 5)
  - Time Canada: 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 490, Folder 6)
  - Time Canada: 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 490, Folder 7)
  - Time Canada: 1970 (Offsite-box 490, Folder 8)
  - Time Canada: 1971 (Offsite-box 490, Folder 9-10)